<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 10:27:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Welcome to Joplin!</title>
      <link>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/be76d6d99d81444394bc206e08a8e80c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/be76d6d99d81444394bc206e08a8e80c/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Joplin! Joplin is a free, open source note taking and to-do application, which helps you write and organise your notes, and synchronise them between your devices. The notes are searchable, can be copied, tagged and modified either from the application directly or from your own text editor. The notes are in Markdown format. Joplin is available as a desktop, mobile and terminal application.
The notes in this notebook give an overview of what Joplin can do and how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Importing and exporting notes</title>
      <link>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/2ba8366ac77c4a93b9eb7595d1343eb6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/2ba8366ac77c4a93b9eb7595d1343eb6/</guid>
      <description>Importing and exporting notes Importing from Evernote Joplin can import complete Evernote notebooks, as well as notes, tags, images, attached files and note metadata (such as author, geo-location, etc.) via ENEX files.
To import Evernote data, first export your Evernote notebooks to ENEX files as described here. Then, on desktop, do the following: Open File &amp;gt; Import &amp;gt; ENEX and select your file. The notes will be imported into a new separate notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Synchronising your notes</title>
      <link>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/6651b9db52e14d278c6134166a4ef71d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/6651b9db52e14d278c6134166a4ef71d/</guid>
      <description>Synchronising your notes Joplin allows you to synchronise your data using various file hosting services. The supported cloud services are the following:
Setting up Joplin Cloud synchronisation Joplin Cloud is a web service specifically designed for Joplin. Besides synchronising your data, it also allows you to publish a note to the internet, or share a notebook with your friends, family or colleagues. Joplin Cloud, compared to other services, also features a number of performance improvements allowing for faster synchronisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Tips</title>
      <link>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/132e470f077b4299a3db1560b8481bd4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/132e470f077b4299a3db1560b8481bd4/</guid>
      <description>Tips The first few notes should have given you an overview of the main functionalities of Joplin, but there&amp;rsquo;s more it can do. See below for some of these features and how to get more help using the app:
Web clipper The Web Clipper is a browser extension that allows you to save web pages and screenshots from your browser. To start using it, open the Joplin desktop application, go to the Web Clipper Options and follow the instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Joplin Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/6649f36bf0ff4aa3ba26f30c808228c0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mami.rxliuli.com/demo/joplin2hugo/posts/6649f36bf0ff4aa3ba26f30c808228c0/</guid>
      <description>Joplin Privacy Policy The Joplin applications, including the Android, iOS, Windows, macOS and Linux applications, do not send any data to any service without your authorisation. Any data that Joplin saves, such as notes or images, are saved to your own device and you are free to delete this data at any time.
If you choose to synchronise with a third-party, such as OneDrive or Dropbox, the notes will be sent to that account, in which case the third-party privacy policy applies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
